<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hollywood &#8211; Boxoffice Updates</title>
	<atom:link href="https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/category/hollywood/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:26:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Little Mermaid Movie Review: Disney’s live-action adaptation soars, thanks to Halle Bailey</title>
		<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-little-mermaid-movie-review-disneys-live-action-adaptation-soars-thanks-to-halle-bailey/</link>
					<comments>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-little-mermaid-movie-review-disneys-live-action-adaptation-soars-thanks-to-halle-bailey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Directed by Rob Marshall, The Little Mermaid released in cinemas on May 26, 2023. Here&#8217;s our review of the film. By Tushar Joshi: In the movies of all Disney movies, the story of a little girl under the ocean falling in love with a guy who lives above the water is perhaps a tale that’s]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Directed by Rob Marshall, The Little Mermaid released in cinemas on May 26, 2023. Here&#8217;s our review of the film.</p>



<p>By Tushar Joshi: In the movies of all Disney movies, the story of a little girl under the ocean falling in love with a guy who lives above the water is perhaps a tale that’s absolutely special. The Little Mermaid’s 1989 animated version is one of the most underrated Disney movie of all time. The visuals, colours, the songs all just worked together in sync to create a masterpiece. So when Disney announced they are reprising the film as a live-action adaptation, some eyes rolled with a long drawn ‘why?’. Fortunately, when Halle Bailey was announced as the lead face as Ariel, there was some excitement and a sigh of relief.</p>



<p>In the 2023 live-action version of The Little Mermaid, the makers have gone all out to ensure each and every character has been given ample footage. The VFX used to show Ariel’s tail, the scales on her body glistening as she rises up, the myriad of colours that reflect the sunlight in the ocean, all of these elements are just superb. If you have watched the 1989 version, then certain scenes are almost a mirror image. Melissa McCarthy who’s often cast as a comic character, has been given a makeover as the menacing villain Ursula and have to say she sadly falls short of the mark in her performance.</p>



<p>The music is a definite highlight of the film with Halle showing off her vocals as she impeccably hits those high notes. Being a professional singer has definitely helped her give Ariel that extra edge. Where the film falters though is on the emotional connect. The CGI and special effects are visually dazzling, but on paper the screenplay lacks depth.<br>The Little Mermaid is a visual treat. The songs are great, the scenes between Ariel and Flounder (Jacob Tremblay), Sebastian (Daveed Diggs) and Scuttle (Awkafina) are top notch. If you love Halle’s music and a good Disney musical, then you are in for an enchanting dive under water.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-little-mermaid-movie-review-disneys-live-action-adaptation-soars-thanks-to-halle-bailey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Martin Scorsese announces film on Jesus after meeting Pope Francis in Vatican</title>
		<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/martin-scorsese-announces-film-on-jesus-after-meeting-pope-francis-in-vatican/</link>
					<comments>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/martin-scorsese-announces-film-on-jesus-after-meeting-pope-francis-in-vatican/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Veteran director Martin Scorsese met The Pope in Vatican City on May 27. Just a day later, on May 28, he announced that he wanted to make a film focusing on Jesus Christ. The director is currently touring Italy. Veteran director Martin Scorsese, who is known to be religious, recently met The Pope in Vatican]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Veteran director Martin Scorsese met The Pope in Vatican City on May 27. Just a day later, on May 28, he announced that he wanted to make a film focusing on Jesus Christ. The director is currently touring Italy.</p>



<p>Veteran director Martin Scorsese, who is known to be religious, recently met The Pope in Vatican City. He and his wife, Helen Morris, had a brief meeting with Pope Francis on May 27 and just a day later, the director announced that he would be making a film on Jesus Christ.</p>



<p>MARTIN SCORSESE TO MAKE A FILM ON JESUS CHRIST<br>Martin Scorsese, who is known for films like Goodfellas, Shutter Island, The Wolf of Wall Street and The Irishman, has announced that he will be directing a film on Jesus. This announcement came just a day after he met the Pope in Vatican City. The director is currently touring Italy post his appearance in the Cannes Film Festival.</p>



<p>READ | DYK Shah Rukh Khan, Leonardo DiCaprio were to co-star in a Martin Scorsese-produced Hollywood film?</p>



<p>“I have responded to the Pope’s appeal to artists in the only way I know how: by imagining and writing a screenplay for a film about Jesus,&#8221; Scorsese said in a conference held at the Vatican. &#8220;And I’m about to start making it,&#8221; he added without elaborating more on the project.</p>



<p>On Saturday, May 27, Scorsese and his wife Helen Morris had a brief meeting with Pope Francis at the Vatican before attending the conference, which was headlined The Global Aesthetics of the Catholic Imagination. It was organized by Georgetown University. The editor of the religious magazine La Civilta Cattolica, Antonio Spadaro, stated on the website of the publication that during their talk at the conference, Scorsese alternated between references to his films and personal tales and revealed how the Holy Father&#8217;s appeal to let us see Jesus moved him among other things.</p>



<p>ABOUT MARTIN SCORCESE<br>Martin Scorsese is a legendary American filmmaker who has helmed films like The Wolf of Wall Street, Shutter Island, The Last Temptation of Christ and many other classic films. He has served as an essential figure of the New Hollywood Era. His last work, Killers of The Red Moon, was screened at Cannes. It is scheduled to be released in select theaters on October 6, before a wide release in the United States on October 20, by Paramount Pictures. It is also set for an unspecified streaming release on Apple TV+</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/martin-scorsese-announces-film-on-jesus-after-meeting-pope-francis-in-vatican/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
