<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>paglaadmin &#8211; Boxoffice Updates</title>
	<atom:link href="https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/author/paglaadmin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:26:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Little Mermaid Movie Review: Disney’s live-action adaptation soars, thanks to Halle Bailey</title>
		<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-little-mermaid-movie-review-disneys-live-action-adaptation-soars-thanks-to-halle-bailey/</link>
					<comments>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-little-mermaid-movie-review-disneys-live-action-adaptation-soars-thanks-to-halle-bailey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Directed by Rob Marshall, The Little Mermaid released in cinemas on May 26, 2023. Here&#8217;s our review of the film. By Tushar Joshi: In the movies of all Disney movies, the story of a little girl under the ocean falling in love with a guy who lives above the water is perhaps a tale that’s]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Directed by Rob Marshall, The Little Mermaid released in cinemas on May 26, 2023. Here&#8217;s our review of the film.</p>



<p>By Tushar Joshi: In the movies of all Disney movies, the story of a little girl under the ocean falling in love with a guy who lives above the water is perhaps a tale that’s absolutely special. The Little Mermaid’s 1989 animated version is one of the most underrated Disney movie of all time. The visuals, colours, the songs all just worked together in sync to create a masterpiece. So when Disney announced they are reprising the film as a live-action adaptation, some eyes rolled with a long drawn ‘why?’. Fortunately, when Halle Bailey was announced as the lead face as Ariel, there was some excitement and a sigh of relief.</p>



<p>In the 2023 live-action version of The Little Mermaid, the makers have gone all out to ensure each and every character has been given ample footage. The VFX used to show Ariel’s tail, the scales on her body glistening as she rises up, the myriad of colours that reflect the sunlight in the ocean, all of these elements are just superb. If you have watched the 1989 version, then certain scenes are almost a mirror image. Melissa McCarthy who’s often cast as a comic character, has been given a makeover as the menacing villain Ursula and have to say she sadly falls short of the mark in her performance.</p>



<p>The music is a definite highlight of the film with Halle showing off her vocals as she impeccably hits those high notes. Being a professional singer has definitely helped her give Ariel that extra edge. Where the film falters though is on the emotional connect. The CGI and special effects are visually dazzling, but on paper the screenplay lacks depth.<br>The Little Mermaid is a visual treat. The songs are great, the scenes between Ariel and Flounder (Jacob Tremblay), Sebastian (Daveed Diggs) and Scuttle (Awkafina) are top notch. If you love Halle’s music and a good Disney musical, then you are in for an enchanting dive under water.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-little-mermaid-movie-review-disneys-live-action-adaptation-soars-thanks-to-halle-bailey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Martin Scorsese announces film on Jesus after meeting Pope Francis in Vatican</title>
		<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/martin-scorsese-announces-film-on-jesus-after-meeting-pope-francis-in-vatican/</link>
					<comments>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/martin-scorsese-announces-film-on-jesus-after-meeting-pope-francis-in-vatican/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Veteran director Martin Scorsese met The Pope in Vatican City on May 27. Just a day later, on May 28, he announced that he wanted to make a film focusing on Jesus Christ. The director is currently touring Italy. Veteran director Martin Scorsese, who is known to be religious, recently met The Pope in Vatican]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Veteran director Martin Scorsese met The Pope in Vatican City on May 27. Just a day later, on May 28, he announced that he wanted to make a film focusing on Jesus Christ. The director is currently touring Italy.</p>



<p>Veteran director Martin Scorsese, who is known to be religious, recently met The Pope in Vatican City. He and his wife, Helen Morris, had a brief meeting with Pope Francis on May 27 and just a day later, the director announced that he would be making a film on Jesus Christ.</p>



<p>MARTIN SCORSESE TO MAKE A FILM ON JESUS CHRIST<br>Martin Scorsese, who is known for films like Goodfellas, Shutter Island, The Wolf of Wall Street and The Irishman, has announced that he will be directing a film on Jesus. This announcement came just a day after he met the Pope in Vatican City. The director is currently touring Italy post his appearance in the Cannes Film Festival.</p>



<p>READ | DYK Shah Rukh Khan, Leonardo DiCaprio were to co-star in a Martin Scorsese-produced Hollywood film?</p>



<p>“I have responded to the Pope’s appeal to artists in the only way I know how: by imagining and writing a screenplay for a film about Jesus,&#8221; Scorsese said in a conference held at the Vatican. &#8220;And I’m about to start making it,&#8221; he added without elaborating more on the project.</p>



<p>On Saturday, May 27, Scorsese and his wife Helen Morris had a brief meeting with Pope Francis at the Vatican before attending the conference, which was headlined The Global Aesthetics of the Catholic Imagination. It was organized by Georgetown University. The editor of the religious magazine La Civilta Cattolica, Antonio Spadaro, stated on the website of the publication that during their talk at the conference, Scorsese alternated between references to his films and personal tales and revealed how the Holy Father&#8217;s appeal to let us see Jesus moved him among other things.</p>



<p>ABOUT MARTIN SCORCESE<br>Martin Scorsese is a legendary American filmmaker who has helmed films like The Wolf of Wall Street, Shutter Island, The Last Temptation of Christ and many other classic films. He has served as an essential figure of the New Hollywood Era. His last work, Killers of The Red Moon, was screened at Cannes. It is scheduled to be released in select theaters on October 6, before a wide release in the United States on October 20, by Paramount Pictures. It is also set for an unspecified streaming release on Apple TV+</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/martin-scorsese-announces-film-on-jesus-after-meeting-pope-francis-in-vatican/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Kerala Story box office collection Day 25: Adah Sharma&#8217;s film slows down, mints just Rs 2 crore</title>
		<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-kerala-story-box-office-collection-day-25-adah-sharmas-film-slows-down-mints-just-rs-2-crore/</link>
					<comments>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-kerala-story-box-office-collection-day-25-adah-sharmas-film-slows-down-mints-just-rs-2-crore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bollywood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Adah Sharma&#8217;s film The Kerala Story is seeing a drop in its box office collection now. However, it still has the potential to cross the Rs 250-crore mark. By Grace Cyril: Sudipto Sen&#8217;s directorial venture The Kerla Story recently crossed the Rs 200-crore mark at the box office. It has now slowed down in its]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Adah Sharma&#8217;s film The Kerala Story is seeing a drop in its box office collection now. However, it still has the potential to cross the Rs 250-crore mark.</p>



<p>By Grace Cyril: Sudipto Sen&#8217;s directorial venture The Kerla Story recently crossed the Rs 200-crore mark at the box office. It has now slowed down in its collection. On Day 25, May 29, the film minted its lowest yet, that is, Rs 2.10 crore. Nevertheless, TKS has created quite a roar at the box office and is expected to cross the Rs 250-crore mark soon. The film delves into the serious subject of religious conversions, the ISIS, and chronicles around three women.</p>



<p>THE KERALA STORY BOX OFFICE COLLECTION<br>Amid all the controversies surrounding The Kerala Story, the film released on May 5. Ever since, it has been doing incredibly well at the box office. On Day 18, the film even managed to cross the Rs 200-crore club. After crossing that milestone, TKS slowed down in its collection. As per the early trade estimates, on Day 25, the film minted Rs 2.10 crore at the box office. Hence, the total collection of The Kerala Story now stands at Rs 227.07 crore. It had an overall 10.30 per cent occupancy in Hindi on May 28.</p>



<p>ABOUT THE KERALA STORY<br>The Kerala Story follows the story of a Hindu woman from Kerala, played by Adah Sharma. She is brainwashed to embrace Islam and sent to Syria, where she is forced to join the ISIS terrorist organisation. She is tortured there. The film is directed by Sudipto Sen and produced by Vipul Amrutlal Shah. The Kerala Story has been in the scanner ever since the trailer was released.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/the-kerala-story-box-office-collection-day-25-adah-sharmas-film-slows-down-mints-just-rs-2-crore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jogira Sara Ra Ra box office collection Day 4: Nawazuddin Siddiqui&#8217;s film struggles to reach a mere Rs 2 crore</title>
		<link>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/jogira-sara-ra-ra-box-office-collection-day-4-nawazuddin-siddiquis-film-struggles-to-reach-a-mere-rs-2-crore/</link>
					<comments>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/jogira-sara-ra-ra-box-office-collection-day-4-nawazuddin-siddiquis-film-struggles-to-reach-a-mere-rs-2-crore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bollywood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Neha Sharma&#8217;s film Jogira Sara Ra Ra is not doing well at the box office. It is struggling to mint a mere total of Rs 2 crore. By Grace Cyril: Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Neha Sharma&#8217;s latest release Jogira Sara Ra Ra is a huge disaster. The film has proved to be a]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Neha Sharma&#8217;s film Jogira Sara Ra Ra is not doing well at the box office. It is struggling to mint a mere total of Rs 2 crore.</p>



<p>By Grace Cyril: Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Neha Sharma&#8217;s latest release Jogira Sara Ra Ra is a huge disaster. The film has proved to be a box office dud. In four days, Jogira Sara Ra Ra failed to even cross Rs 2 crore.</p>



<p>JOGIRA SARA RA RA BOX OFFICE COLLECTION<br>Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Neha Sharma&#8217;s Jogira Sara Ra Ra released on May 26 in theatres. The film received mixed reviews from critics. On Day 1, the film minted just Rs 50 lakh, which is very less. On Day 4, May 29, the film reportedly minted just Rs 32 lakh. The total collection now stands at Rs 1.83 crore.</p>



<p>ABOUT JOGIRA SARA RA RA<br>Jogira Sara Ra Ra stars Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Neha Sharma in lead roles. It is produced by Naeem A Siddiqui of Touchwood Multimedia Creations. It has Kiran Shyam Shroff as its creative producer. The film released in theatres on May 26. Directed by Kushan Nandy, the family comedy also stars Sanjay Mishra and Mahaakshay Chakraborty. Kushan and Nawazuddin previously worked together on Babumoshai Bandookbaaz (2020).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://boxoffice.townhallseattle.org/jogira-sara-ra-ra-box-office-collection-day-4-nawazuddin-siddiquis-film-struggles-to-reach-a-mere-rs-2-crore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
